[{"answer": "Well, so far, so good.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 14, "question": "Robert Redford, how are you?", "qSentId": 13}, {"answer": "Well, I made her do that.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 26, "question": "EDFORD: Oh, you like that?", "qSentId": 25}, {"answer": "That's a good question.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 40, "question": "Do you get hundreds, thousands, possibly in your case, millions of people telling you how they've changed their lives because you've had their lives altered?", "qSentId": 39}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 47, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 46}, {"answer": "Well, I'm wrong.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 49, "question": "Even with \"All the President's Men\"?", "qSentId": 48}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 62, "question": "You think?", "qSentId": 61}, {"answer": "And I think it worked out pretty well.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 65, "question": "I guess OK with your wife, huh?", "qSentId": 64}, {"answer": "Well, not all of them, no.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 102, "question": "I heard that you don't watch your own movies?", "qSentId": 101}, {"answer": "-- that it was a good movie.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 116, "question": "When was that?", "qSentId": 115}, {"answer": "Three years ago.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 118, "question": "When did you watch it?", "qSentId": 117}, {"answer": "I saw it with my family three years ago.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 120, "question": "You first saw \"The Sting\" three years ago?", "qSentId": 119}, {"answer": "For my mind -- it was a good movie.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 124, "question": "What did you think?", "qSentId": 123}, {"answer": "I did see \"Butch Cassidy.\"", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 129, "question": "Have you seen \"Butch Cassidy\"?", "qSentId": 128}, {"answer": "No, we'll jump.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 143, "question": "Ready?", "qSentId": 142}, {"answer": "When I --", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 151, "question": "-- what goes through your mind?", "qSentId": 150}, {"answer": "Well, seeing that of course reminds me of my good friend Paul.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 153, "question": "When you watch these films decades later?", "qSentId": 152}, {"answer": "I think the -- yes.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 162, "question": "Do you have a favorite Redford movie?", "qSentId": 161}, {"answer": "I'm a good shot.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 176, "question": "How good of a shot are you?", "qSentId": 175}, {"answer": "I love -- I love -- I had a gun -- they gave me a gun two weeks before the film and I would strap on a holster and as you walk on, just drawing whenever I could because I want to be able to not have them speed up the camera so it was fun.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 185, "question": "You (INAUDIBLE) shots?", "qSentId": 184}, {"answer": "Well, I've enjoyed a lot of the films that I've made.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 191, "question": "But if you were able to, which -- other than \"Butch Cassidy\" which parts of your film career would you most like people to focus on?", "qSentId": 190}, {"answer": "\"Ordinary People\" because that was the first directing job.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 198, "question": "\"Ordinary People\"?", "qSentId": 197}, {"answer": "He had a very short attention span.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 206, "question": "What kind of man was he?", "qSentId": 205}, {"answer": "I don't know.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 242, "question": "CAVOY: Where is his (INAUDIBLE)?", "qSentId": 241}, {"answer": "I don't think it was exclusive.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 263, "question": "Did you see a parallel between actions taken by the Bush administration, for example, after 9/11, and what you saw in your movie?", "qSentId": 262}, {"answer": "Yes, I think -- it's a twofold.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 272, "question": "That it mattered to you?", "qSentId": 271}, {"answer": "It was quite -- I suppose it wasn't that difficult of a thing.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 293, "question": "How was it for you to immerse yourself in the American civil war like this?", "qSentId": 292}, {"answer": "Well, he's very good.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 313, "question": "What happens then for a young actor?", "qSentId": 312}, {"answer": "You feel like you should be calling him Sir Robert, but anyway --", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 319, "question": "Did you?", "qSentId": 318}, {"answer": "Yes, please rewind it.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 323, "question": "Did you call Robert Redford Bob?", "qSentId": 322}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 334, "question": "Can I just say one thing about James?", "qSentId": 333}, {"answer": "She didn't need to because I wanted her -- I wanted James and Robin Wright off the bat.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 363, "question": "What?", "qSentId": 362}, {"answer": "I didn't read the script.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 368, "question": "Robin?", "qSentId": 367}, {"answer": "I read it after I met with you.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 381, "question": "You never read the script?", "qSentId": 380}, {"answer": "You don't mind if I'm not here for -- (LAUGHTER)", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 388, "question": "Your power knows -- it just has no bounds, is it?", "qSentId": 387}, {"answer": "Well, I wouldn't -- I mean the parallel is there --", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 418, "question": "I mean do you believe looking what happened in your movie, that what's going on now with Guantanamo is fundamentally wrong, that it's unjust?", "qSentId": 417}, {"answer": "Or Rumsfeld or a combination thereof.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 424, "question": "Well, you played a Dick Cheney role, don't you really?", "qSentId": 423}, {"answer": "Bob party.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 451, "question": "Bob party?", "qSentId": 450}, {"answer": "I wouldn't -- I wouldn't even view it.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 459, "question": "And how would you view a country ran by Sarah Palin?", "qSentId": 458}, {"answer": "Awesome.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 470, "question": "What's your take on America?", "qSentId": 469}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 486, "question": "And do you admire that?", "qSentId": 485}, {"answer": "I don't know what the question is, this is a developing patent that I'm concerned about.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 525, "question": "And your question is?", "qSentId": 524}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 539, "question": "Could you?", "qSentId": 538}, {"answer": "Well, that's a big question.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 546, "question": "When you see what's going on in Guantanamo Bay, for example, what do you think?", "qSentId": 545}, {"answer": "EDFORD: In terms of the Guantanamo issue, I'm going to now be political and tell you, I don't -- I'm not comfortable because of the film.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 554, "question": "and I think that given the premise of your movie, Robert, I mean, do you share that discomfort that your president right now has allowed Guantanamo to continue, when he said that he'd shut it down?", "qSentId": 553}, {"answer": "It's a true story.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 586, "question": "Was he wrong?", "qSentId": 585}, {"answer": "It starts with craft.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 627, "question": "What do you look for in a great actor or actress?", "qSentId": 626}, {"answer": "It was where do I sign, actually.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 639, "question": "Where do I sign?", "qSentId": 638}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 645, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 644}, {"answer": "Oh, wow, I'm just very humbled by everyone sitting at this table right now, and just honored to be a part of it.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 648, "question": "When you work with a cast as talented and varied as this?", "qSentId": 647}, {"answer": "Especially you.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 651, "question": "Include this part of the table?", "qSentId": 650}, {"answer": "No, no.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 655, "question": "Did you ever imagine when you were young, you would call Robert Redford Bob?", "qSentId": 654}, {"answer": "Fortunately, no.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 669, "question": "Have you ever had anything in your life where you had to make a decision of that kind of magnitude?", "qSentId": 668}, {"answer": "CAVOY: He is.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 698, "question": "Not bearding off, but on the humor level, I mean, is he as mischievous as I would hope he'd be on a movie set?", "qSentId": 697}, {"answer": "I think I have about 60 new crow's feet thanks to the -- we laughed so much.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 703, "question": "Was it good fun to make this film?", "qSentId": 702}, {"answer": "Oh, that was the dream man.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 733, "question": "Why am I just finding that out now?", "qSentId": 732}, {"answer": "Somehow it's gone out of my mind.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 737, "question": "What movies have you done, Bob?", "qSentId": 736}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 741, "question": "That was you, wasn't it?", "qSentId": 740}, {"answer": "I like al of them.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 752, "question": "Tom?", "qSentId": 751}, {"answer": "Well, I'm going to have to say \"Butch Cassidy and the Sundance Kid.\"", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 761, "question": "Ellen?", "qSentId": 760}, {"answer": "Yeah.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 768, "question": "That you wrote?", "qSentId": 767}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 770, "question": "You want to sing it?", "qSentId": 769}, {"answer": "Maybe later.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 773, "question": "Bended knee?", "qSentId": 772}, {"answer": "Yeah, I am.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 779, "question": "You must be ready for one, aren't you?", "qSentId": 778}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 783, "question": "Have you got one in the pipeline?", "qSentId": 782}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 787, "question": "-- clues?", "qSentId": 786}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 789, "question": "Any co-stars?", "qSentId": 788}, {"answer": "I think she has all the rights.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 801, "question": "Does she start all the sequel rumors?", "qSentId": 800}, {"answer": "I actually just finished another political film called \"The Ides of March.\"", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 803, "question": "Evan, what are you up to next?", "qSentId": 802}, {"answer": "Oh, don't make me choose.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 809, "question": "Clooney or Redford?", "qSentId": 808}, {"answer": "Don't know.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 814, "question": "Tom, what are you up to?", "qSentId": 813}, {"answer": "I'm not sure yet.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 816, "question": "Not sure yet?", "qSentId": 815}, {"answer": "There is a Ulysses S. Grant role that's coming up, which is quite good.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 821, "question": "-- quintet?", "qSentId": 820}, {"answer": "Oh, yeah.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 824, "question": "And isn't there a movie with Judi Dench?", "qSentId": 823}, {"answer": "Don't know.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 827, "question": "When is that coming out?", "qSentId": 826}, {"answer": "I've shot a film that some -- with Lawrence Kasdan directing, with Diane Keaton and Diane Wiest, a wonderful cast.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 832, "question": "Kevin, what are you going to be up to next?", "qSentId": 831}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 835, "question": "Comedy?", "qSentId": 834}, {"answer": "Still shooting \"Girl With the Dragon Tattoo.\"", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 846, "question": "Robin, next project?", "qSentId": 845}, {"answer": "We thought there would be a sequel to \"the Conspirator.\"", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 848, "question": "And any truth you're never going to work with McAvoy again?", "qSentId": 847}, {"answer": "I'm going to do a film called \"Welcome to the Punch\" in London.", "docId": "110411pmt", "aSentId": 852, "question": "James, what's in the pipeline for you?", "qSentId": 851}]